Bella, Gloria, love.
Oh.
How are you?
Oh, I'm OK.
I will be.
I said she could stay with us tomorrow
just until she feels better.
Yeah.
Of course she can.
No, things won't be for long.
Well, you can stay as long as you want, my love.
I've really missed you.
Pops.
Great to see you, love.
Oh.
All right, shall we get you off to bed then?
You should have given me some warm.
I know.
I'll have to put the electric blanket on.
I'm sorry.
All right, Bella.
Freezing up there.
In a bedroom, Peter unpacks her suitcase.
The middle-aged woman opens her green case.
Do you want your PJs?
Yeah.
Lifting a bundle of pajamas, Peter finds a sheet of paper
labeled Lancaster North Hospital discharge sheet.
He closes the suitcase and brings Gloria the pajamas.
There you go.
Thank you.
He picks up the locket.
He kept it.
Oh, cool.